designdeal.com 2016-10-22

# DESIGNDEAL | Websites for Online Shopping in India | Original Art Prints Online

Design Deal India Private Limited is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to the site. Your use of the site confirms your acceptance of the site. On registering on our site, we also collect personal information such as your phone number, billing and shipping addresses and credit card information, buying preferences, etc. We also collect other information such as browsing history on the site, through the use of cookies and other technologies. You can also invite friends by giving name and email address amongst other information. We use this information to try and better our services and shopping experience for you as well as notify you on future sales to enhance your experience with us.

In case of change of control of the company, merger, acquisition, or part sale, or cross promotions, corporate tie-ups, general promotions, etc personal information may be transferred and these terms and conditions would stand unless stated otherwise. We may also need to transfer personal information if required by an order from the Government of India.

We are committed to protecting the information that you provide and while we cannot guarantee the protection of this information, we will take all reasonable steps to ensure that we do our best towards protecting the confidentiality of data stored.

Our payment gateway partner will ensure stringent security measures to ensure that critically sensitive information, such as personal information and credit card details, are extremely well protected. The information is encrypted before it is transmitted over the Internet to the payment gateway and the payment gateway partner does not store any credit card details for security reasons.

If you are no longer interested in receiving e-mail communication and information from us please send us an email at [support@designdeal.com](mailto:support@designdeal.com)

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we shall amend this on the site and your continued use of the site indicates your acceptance to the Privacy Policy.

If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us anytime at [support@designdeal.com](mailto:support@designdeal.com)
